YUSUF DALBUDAK



🖈 Tevfik Bey Neighborhood, Yakut Street, Block A, No:2, Apartment:2, Sefaköy-Küçükçekmece/Istanbul, 34290 İSTANBUL 📞

05392079421

■ yusufdalbudak2121@gmail.com

Date of birth Gender Place of birth **Nationality** 16-01-2001 Male **TURK** Mersin

Marital status **Driving license** LinkedIn

SİNGLE https://www.linkedin.com/in/yusuf-

dalbudak-6494aa23b/

As a communication assistant at DenizBank, responsible for managing internal and external communication channels, coordinating meetings and events, and assisting in the development and execution of communication strategies. Successfully improved team collaboration and efficiency through effective communication and organizational skills. Additionally, made significant progress in cybersecurity by developing skills in intrusion detection systems (IDS), machine learning for network analysis, and hands-on experience with tools like Wireshark and Python for real-time network scanning.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Account Specialist Sep 2018 - Jul 2019

Tam Plastic Braiform, Istanbul

Guest Coordinator Aug 2020 - Jul 2021

Business Channel Turk Tv, Istanbul

Communication Assistant Mar 2024 - Jun 2024

DENİZBANK AŞ., İSTANBUL

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

Managment Information System Sep 2020 - Jul 2024

Istanbul Topkapi University, Istanbul

Public Relations Sep 2015 - Sep 2019

Gurpinar Trade Vocational High School, Istanbul

Certified Cybersecurity Architect Apr 2023 - Jun 2023

SoftITo Academy, İSTANBUL

Completed Cybersecurity Architect training program.

SKILLS

Teamwork, Leadership Experienced Kali Linux Experienced Skillful **Firewall**

Incident Response and Threat

Skillful **Analysis**

Security Standards and

Compliance Skillful Skillful Cryptography **Programming/Scripting** Skillful **Analytical Thinking** Skillful **Problem Solving** Expert Communication Expert

CISSP, CEH, CompTIA Security+ Skillful

IDS/IPS Experienced

VPNs Skillful

REFERENCES

Assistant Professor Alp Par, Ph.D.

0530 360 00 58

alppar@topkapi.edu.tr

Istanbul Topkapı University

Nagihan Kartal

0554 794 26 67

nagihankartal@topkapi.edu.tr

Istanbul Topkapi University

PUBLICATIONS

For My projects click the Link: https://github.com/yusufdalbudak

LANGUAGES

English B2

COURSES	
Introduction to Forensic IT BTK Academy	Jul 2023 - Jul 2023
Kali Linux BTK Academy	Jul 2023 - Jul 2023
Linux Operating System in Cyber Security BTK Academy	Jul 2023 - Jul 2023
Cyber Security Architect Istanbul Chamber of Commerce SoftITo IT Academy	Apr 2023 - Jun 2023
NSE 1 Network Security Associate Fortinet	Aug 2023 - Aug 2023
NSE 2 Network Security Associate Fortinet	Aug 2023 - Aug 2023
Python For Cyber Security BTK Academy	Aug 2023 - Aug 2023
Introduction to Cyber Security Cisco	Sep 2023 - Aug 2023
FCA-Fortigate 7.4 Operator Self-Paced Fortinet	Sep 2023 - Sep 2023
CEH(Practical Cyber Security and Ethical Hacking Training) Udemy	Sep 2023 - Sep 2023
Introduction to Data Science Cisco	Sep 2023 - Sep 2023
CompTIA Security+(SY0-601)Cert Prep:9 Operations and Incident Response LinkedIn	Oct 2023 - Oct 2023
Artificial Intelligence Engineer Bootcamp Udemy	May 2024 - May 2030
Penetration Testing Essential Training LinkedIn	Jun 2023 - Jul 2030
Cybersecurity Applications with Python BTK Academy	Nov 2023 - Jul 2030
Fortinet Certified Associate Cybersecurity Fortinet	Sep 2023 - Jul 2030
Introduction to Digital Forensics BTK Academy	Sep 2023 - Jul 2030
Cybersecurity Architect SoftlTo Academy	Apr 2023 - Jul 2030